Oh, hello.
Oh my god.
I remember, I remember you.  You are such a lively
woman.  What are you talking about today?  What's
your agenda?
[laughter] Do
you remember me?  Yes,
sure.  How were you?
It was 100 years ago already.
Not 100 years ago, it was uh, in the
month of April, somewhere around the seventeenth or
nineteenth.  To yourself, this is such a
good memory,
right?  At 23:47.
[laughter]
Even 2345.
You're writing something down somewhere, it seems.
[laughter]
Okay.
What are you talking about today?
Such a question.
So, what do you think, is it normal that
Zelensky is reburying
these Melnyks there somewhere else?
Yes, great, of course.  Finally, people
are returning to their homeland.  Yes,
absolutely.
That is, these are Nazi dreams
anyway.  Nazis when they are
Nazis.
If they were Nazis, yes, they would
n’t have been buried there in Germany, yes, in
Notre Dame and so on.  Well, for example,
Bandera is buried in Germany.  How could a
Nazi officially live in
post-war Germany?  How?  Calmly.
How can a Nazi live in Canada?  until
2025.
Can you, can you show me
which one?
Why?  No, you tell me, tell me right from
the start, why he can live in Canada
, but he can’t live in Germany
.  Don't know.  Because in
Germany, yes, it is the country of the victorious
nation.
Why did two Nazis live
in all the countries of the world?
Moscow still lives in Moscow.
Who is this?  Well, take
you for example.
And I [laughter] I am
Putin.
No, no, no, wait.  No no.   Let's
start with me.  Yes.
And what does "Nazi" mean?  So
I don't recognize all other nations,
right?  Because I can't stand it.   Do
n't know.  You know what a Nazi is.
Well, she's a Nazi.  Well, you said you were a
Nazi.  So.
What then?   As
I understand it, a Nazi is a person
who does not recognize only his own
nation.  The rest of the nations get out.
Okay, wait.  But didn’t Bandera
recognize other nations?
And as he said, this is
only
with Jews?  Stop, stop, stop.  There were Jews in the
Ukrainian insurgent army.  No
need, no need.
Yes, the occupiers.
And with other nations, each other.  Well, in
any case, he was probably glorifying
his nation.  Yes, of
course.  And I glorify my nation, and
everyone glorifies their nation.   So.
Yeah.  What's wrong with being glorified by a
nation?  This is not Nazism.
Not Nazism.
Of course not.
That is, you glorify your nation, but
consider all other nations - this is
No.  Stop, stop, stop.  Let's do it this way.
Look, if you Yes,
what is Nazism?
Look again.  If you are
glorifying another nation,
not yet.
What?
What?  What?  What?
Glorification.  Oh, here [laughter] there
is glorification of one’s own nation, and other nations are the
opposite.
So, let's agree that glorifying
your nation does not mean that you
oppress or deny other nations.
Agree, right?  If you say,
for example, we are the best
chess players or football players in the world, this is
glorification of your nation.   What do
nations have to do with chess players?
Well, if, for example, Italians say:
"Italians make the best pizza in the world
."  This is a glorification of the Italian
nation.
Why?  No.
Well, glorification, yes.
No.  How come not?
They claim that their nation
makes the best pizza in the world.  They don't look down
on other
nations, but they say: "Our nation has
such an achievement that...
And what about
Nazism? It's when you say,
for example, that the Russian is the best, and
the other nations are nothing."  Okay,
got it.  All.  Bandera never said
that Russians are the best and that other
nations are nothing.
Bandera didn't say that.   Yes.
And Russian Nazis say things like that, right?   This
means that Bandera is not a Nazi, but Russian
Nazis are.  For example,
Putin.  Putin really says, yes, that
Russians are a chosen nation.
You've confused me, in short.
So, where are you running off to?  Yeah,
listen, let's get started.  Let's start like this then.
That's how it is.
No, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.  Once again
.  Again.
Again.  More.  Hitler is a Nazi.  Yes.  The first
Nazi.  Yes.
After Eva, Braun served Hitler.  Everyone, it
seems to me, was called Nazis.
Okay, yes.  Vlas served Hitler, but
Bandera did not serve Hitler
. He tried to get under his skin.
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
Bandera served Hitler.
Well, he wrote this one again
.  Again.  Bandera served
Hitler, yes.  And this is what is called.   Do
n't interrupt me.
Again.  Bandera served, yes or no?
Just say yes or no?  Hitler served, or did
n't serve, it seems.  No, I didn't serve.  All.
He wrote and wrote this
thing again.  Look at who wrote what to me.
Look, you said that anyone who is a Nazi is
also a Nazi.  Bandera served Hitler, you
said no.  That's it, Bandera is not a
Nazi.
What the hell is this called?
This is called Russian
You.
You are Russian-Russian Nazis, right?
You owe nothing.  Look, now look.  Let's
see what Nazism is like in Russia now
.  Agree?
Yeah.  Come on, come on, speak up.
According to.   I do
n't agree, of course.
Okay, let's see.  Well, in Russia
they say that the Russian nation is the
best.
Who's speaking?
Putin.
Come on, straight ahead.
Now, now straight ahead.  Yeah,
go ahead.
[clears throat]
Right now.   The
greatness of Russia lies in the great
Russian people.  who gave the world
the greatest Russian culture,
incomparable with other cultures of
other peoples.  Putin, 2022, August.   Yes.
But he doesn’t say
that other nations are bad, right?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.  Let's.  So
he does it again,
because Nazism presupposes the
greatness of one’s nation, and other nations,
how is this correct, what word can be
used?   Do
not admit.  I don't know, I just ca
n't admit it.  Right.  Putin does not
recognize Ukrainians.  He says that
Ukrainians do not exist, that they are Russian
people.  Yes, Putin does not recognize the Ukrainian
nation.  Agree.  So he's a Nazi.
Well done.  You said it right.  If he does not
recognize other nations, yes, Putin does not
recognize the Ukrainian nation.  Well done.
Tatar.  And he recognizes the Tatar one.
Look again.  They recognize Ukrainian.
He recognizes this Nazi.
Well, for example, this one, uh,
recognizes Tatar.  Just as Hitler
recognized the Italian nation?  Admitted.
Hitler recognized the Italian nation, he also
recognized it, but he did not recognize some nations
.  The same as Putin.
Some he recognizes, some he doesn't
.  Absolutely correct.
He hasn't recognized Aki yet, except for
Italian.  He probably
didn't recognize anyone anymore.
Why did the Romanian recognize it?  The Japanese were recognized,
the English recognized that these
nations existed, but
for example,
he didn't recognize the Jews, and he doesn't recognize Jews.
You were right when you said that Putin does
n't recognize Ukrainians. It's true, he says, he's
like Carlson, and he said in an interview to the whole world
that Ukrainians don't
exist. Yes, this nation doesn't exist,
Lenin invented it. He was waving some
papers in front of him. Absolutely right. You're a good
man, you helped me. Another
argument is that Putin is a Nazi.  Yes.  Yes.  He
denies the Ukrainian nation.  Absolutely
right.   Yes.
How can you even call Russia
[snorts] a Nazi when there are
almost 200 nationalities in Russia?  How?
Moreover, in Germany during Hitler’s time there
were 148 different nationalities.  Yes.   There
was that too, yes.  And look, Russian,
yes, Russian modern Nazi
society, yes, bans, yes,
national languages, national schools,
for example, how many schools are there in Buryatia, in
Buryatia they closed.  There is not a single school that
teaches in Buryat.  Look.
No, you know that in the Buryat language
it is only optional.  If there are those who
want it, if anyone wants it, please do.
But if there are no people willing to do so, how can
schools be built?
That's right.  Right.  Yes.  Hitler
Hitler said the same thing.  There are no
Jewish applicants for Jewish schools with
Jewish language of instruction.  He said:
"There are no takers."  Just absolutely right.
Well done.
We are right here, point to point.  We are very good with
you.  Yes.  Super.  Let's also now
look at Crimea.  Putin seized Crimea?
No.   So.  Just as
Hitler did not invade
Austria.  Yes, Austria held a referendum
under the presence of Hitler's troops.
Well done.  Another fourth.  So.  Well
done.
How much heart I have,
well done.  Yes, yes.  How many?  Let's.  What
else?  What are other signs of Nazism?  Let's.
We are in Russia now.
Wait.  Which?  Wait.  These are signs of
Nazism.  Why are you taking me away here?  Don't bother
me here.
Okay, let's do it this way.  Omeshevy.  No need.   Let's do it this way
.  In Russia, in Russia, Jews are being persecuted
.  Let's talk about the Buryats.  Are you
talking about the Buryats?  What, have you disappeared
in Russia?  Will Jews be persecuted in Russia?
No, it does
n't.
Well, I don't know.
No, we have a Jewish autonomous region
.  And what?
The one from which all the Jews were expelled.
Less than 10% live there.  How did you
do it?  Jewish,
yes, Jewish autono.  Well, look, you
made them a Jewish autonomous region, in
which less than 10% are Jews.  How so?  What kind of
district did you make?  This is also
absolute, I don’t know about this, of course.
My girlfriend is Jewish, so what?
Look again.  Hitler Hitlergi Hitler did the
same, yes, in this Danzig Dank
Jewish district he did, yes, to
show the League of Nations.  Our Jews
live normally.  Danzin Jewish
District.
in which there were only 10-12% of
Jews left.
Listen, there isn't one.
So
you were the first to give me a heart for the
Buryats.  Yes,
yes,
yes.  Tell me, here
in Russia, we have Ukrainians, they are in second
place, I think
5 million. 5 million, yes, that’s right.
In second place In second place or Tatars In
second place?
5 million Ukrainians, right?  In second place.   Yes.
And so they always ask me:
“Why aren’t there any Ukrainian schools?”
Why?
If, if there was a desire, if there was an
opportunity, if they were in
some specific point,
together somehow,
not scattered throughout the Union, yes,
perhaps they would open Ukrainian schools,
but in any case,
if there is no such, yes, desire, there, in
any case, in any school, for example, in
Buryat, yes, there is [clears throat] the
Buryat language.  Now
early.  You say that there are no Ukrainian schools in the
occupied territories of the Kherson and
Zaporizhzhia regions
, right?  All the schools there were
Ukrainian-language, right?  You closed all the schools there
and switched to Russian as the language of
instruction.  Somehow it
happened that people there were taught
in Ukrainian immediately after the
Russian occupation.
They didn't want it right after the Russian occupation.  They
simply brought them books, all in
Russian, and instruction, and said that now we would
all study in Russian.  Well done.  Another
fifth sign of Nazism.  Yes, absolutely,
yes.  The same as Hitler, yes, Hitler did,
yes, he spoke of Germanization of conquered
territories, yes, the
Russification of conquered territories is also being done.  And
now I'll tell you now, what is your
name?
My channel Subscribe to Gena
Tsidruzni's channel.
Oh, come on.  Ah, come on, talk normally.
You're serious.  Channel Gena about
Belcidrusni.  This is my first name, last name.
Come on, talk.  Come on, remind me.  I remember,
just remind me.  I forgot.
Listen, Gennady Tsidrusni.  Gena
Tsidrusni.
How?  [clears throat] Wait, I'll
tell you everything now.  Some
No something.  [clears throat]
[laughter]
Well, what's wrong with
that?  Go ahead, tell me,
write, don't be
shy.
I'll sign up right away.
Write,
come on.  You, you,
Ivan, Ivan, write.  [laughter]
Ivan, I don’t know your name
for sure.
Ivan,
what's your name?  Well, damn, it's just on the tip of my tongue
.
Listen, come on, come on, while you still have
something on the tip of your tongue, right?  I put something on my
tongue, and now I’ll tell you.
Look what
else you
said about Crimea.
Now now tell me, tell me
about Crimea.  Here is Sevastopol, it has
always been Ukrainian.
Stop.  He was never Ukrainian
at all.  And Khrushchev gave it to him.  Khrushchev
was a tribute king
when Khrushchev gave Crimea away.
He gave Sevastopol away,
yes, in 1954.
Since which one?
He was there in 1954, right?
Sevastopol.  City of all-Union significance.
It was later that they did it.  Then
No, he started right away.  Everything is fine.  Okay, that's
it.
Yes, it always was.
And since when is he ninety?
Was always was always.  Okay, agree.
Now tell me, listen, how did Sevastopol
end up in Russia in 2014?   What do you
mean like a referendum?
No, the referendum was held in Crimea.  And what about
Crimea's accession, right?
And Sevastopol was a separate city.  You
admitted it yourself.  You have a heart.  You I I did
n't catch you.  Yes.  Look, Sevastopol
was a separate entity in Ukraine.  There was the
Autonomous Republic of Crimea and there was
Sevastopol.  Yes, yes.  In Ukraine there were
SSRs that ceased to exist long ago.
Sevastopol in Ukraine.
It was a city of union significance,
right?  And Kyiv and Sevastopol became cities of all-Ukrainian
significance.  We had
two cities of all-Ukrainian significance.
What city?  Oh, since what year?
Since 1991.  Yes, since
1991.  And how did he even re-
Look again, look again, he
was at Sevastopol, I’ll explain.  Yeltsin, yes,
Yeltsin came out in 1991 and Yeltsin
signed and Kravchuk signed.  Everything,
you see, has been signed.
Ukraine, when you
signed the Belvedere Accords on August 24, 1991, and then with Yeltsin
.  Kravchuk gave him some vodka,
he drank it and signed everything.  Now look again
.  Look, now the most important
question.  Are you sure you're running away from
Sevastopol?  Are you running away from
Sevastopol?
Why are you running away?  Who came out first?
Let's talk about Sevastopol first, and I'll
tell you, don't run away from Provo or Russia.
Ukraine, of course, left.  First Ukraine.   Yes.
Now look, if you look, Crimea and
Sevastopol were two different
entities in Ukraine, right?  Uh, Crimea
held a referendum on
Crimea joining Russia, right?  Can you
show me if there was a referendum on
Sevastopol joining Russia?  [laughter]
No, I can't.
No, because there was no such thing.   There
was no Soviet Union.  And what kind of
Soviet Union was it anyway?  What are you doing?  I'm telling you
about 2014.  If you say there was a
referendum, okay, Crimea held a
referendum, yes, but there was no referendum in Sevastopol
about Sevastopol joining the Russian Federation
, that is, joining Russia.   I didn't
understand anything.
What is your name?
Which ballot was it?  What is your
name?  Bulletin.  Do you agree that
Crimea should become part of Russia?   There
was nothing about Sevastopol, only
about Crimea.  No, it was written differently there
.  No need.  Go
find the ballot now.   There
was nothing there about Sevastopol.
So, let's open the bulletin.  Please
read the question in full.
Completely, yes.  Here I opened the ballot.
So, the ballot for voting at the
all-Crimean polling station is all-Crimean, not
Sevastopol.  So, the referendum on
March 16, 2004.  So,
you are in favor of the reunification of Crimea with Russia
as a subject of the Russian Federation.   The
second option is that you are in favor of restoring
the Constitution of the Republic of Crimea of
1992 and for the status of Crimea
as part of Ukraine.  That's it, nothing about Sevastopol
.  It was Crimea that held this
referendum.  Sevastopol did not hold
a referendum on joining Russia.
Crimea.
What?  Sevastopol.
Sevastopol was already part of Ukraine.
As part of Ukraine.  Right.  Right.
But not as part of Crimea.  You shouldn't have
.  They shouldn't have.
Look, Sevastopol was
never part of Crimea.
Oh,
well, you told you right yourself.
Sevastopol was a city of all-Union
significance.  20 hearts.  Come on, take a look.
When did Sevastopol become a city of
union significance?
So, since fifty-four it has
been like this, right?  Since what year?   There
was one before.  Before this it would have been, right?
He wasn't there when Crimea was transferred to Ukraine.
He wasn't.  He wasn’t, but in
1991 he became one in Ukraine.  It just
happened that way, you know?  Because there are no
laws about
them.  Right.  Yes.  And
then you signed, uh, and we signed.
All.  The main thing is that we signed it.  Yes.  It turns out
that Crimea was transferred by referendum, but
Sevastopol did not hold a referendum.
On what basis did you take Sevastopol for yourself
?  But he didn't hold a referendum.
Why didn't you conduct it?  That there were no such
votes at all?  There was none.  What's
there?  The vote was about Crimea.  And what about
Crimea becoming part of Russia,
right?  But there was no Sevastopol.
So you want to say that Crimea
went to Russia, and Sevastopol to
Ukraine?
No, wait, it turns out, look,
Crimea, you say, well, you say
that Crimea held a referendum, but
Sevastopol did not hold a referendum.
Well, yes,
well, that's logical.  It was a separate entity.
By the way, you said it correctly.  Do you see?
Well, to the heart.
Yeah [laughter]
no, wait.  Sevastopol.  Sevastopol,
then, from 1954 to
1991.
What kind of city was it anyway?  Where?  To whom?
What?  Who owned what?  Look, I'm
explaining.  I don't know.  The history of my
country begins on August 24, ninety-
one.  So Ukraine appeared on
August 24, 1991.  Yes.  All.
And Russia also appeared then, as the
Soviet Union collapsed.  Here we are,
emerging from the ruins of the Soviet Union.
Before that, Rurik sailed to Ladoga and so
on.  We showed up and we signed
mutual recognition documents.  Yes,
Ukraine recognized Russia, Russia recognized Ukraine.
They signed an agreement in 1997 on friendship and
cooperation, recognizing
each other's borders and so on.  Yes, Russia
never said that Sevastopol is a
city that belongs to Russia.  She
recognized this city as Ukrainian.  All.
Well, what difference does it make what happened before
1991?  Everything is, uh, an agreement,
yes, a contract.  We, you recognized, we
recognized.  What's the problem?  Yes.
What's there?  Rurik sailed to Sevastopol, and
Khan Baty sailed to Sevastopol.
Nobody was interested anymore.
In general, we have a common history.  I do
n't know why everyone is arguing about this.  I
also don’t know why
we have this territory that
was, it was we who were together
until two,
well, until when we united in the USSR,
we were together,
but the only thing is, well, there was no Ukraine, there
was just territory.  It's just that this is what
you start
arguing about.  You are really worried.
Maybe you can tell me about one
territory?  For example, my
city is Khmelnitsky.  Yes.  Uh, this is Podol,
right?  Podolia.  Well,
you tell me now, Yeah.  Where am I from?
Well, come on, yes, let's take it.  In the 15th century,
yes.  In what single state were we?
Come on, come on, what are you saying?  Well, now I'll
tell you about the 15th century.
Well, look, my city of Khmelnitsky ended up
in Russia, yes, in the 16th century
during the partition of Poland.
Well,
well,
it wasn’t even Ukraine.  Well no,
wait.
No, look, when was the last time you and I were
in the same country?
Yes, yes, well, the territories were growing, in any
case, Tsarist Russia was growing with
territories, it was growing, ...
Ukraine
existed, but it simply wasn't called
Ukraine. There was
no such country.  There was none.  There was none.
It was Lenin who came up with this.  Well, Lenin
came up with it.  Agreed.  Everyone knows this.  It is written in our
textbooks that Lenin came up with it.   He seemed to have come up with it
,
well, how he drew it, created it,
drew it.  He was a draftsman.  He loved, he
drew Ukraine, he drew Belarus, he
drew Kazakhstan.  He
was so rare.  Yes.  [laughter]
Listen, you have to agree that everything stems from how
Rurik arrived.
Oh, you're fed up with this Rurik.
Wait.  Well, it all started from him.  Look,
before Rurik there was nothing.  By the way, the
first capital of Rus',
Kyiv, is the only capital of Rus', the first and the
last.  Ah,
well, go ahead, open Wikipedia and see,
Rus' appeared in 820 or 862, right?
And the city of Kyiv, yes, the capital, 862.
Listen, [laughter] this is your Ukrainian Wikipedia, right
?
No, Russian.  Russian.  Russian
Wikipedia too.  Come in and take a look.  Come in and
take a look.  Let me open it.
Let's open it.   The
capital of Rus'.
Let's.
Not Kievan, but Rus.
Yes, she was alone.  There were no
Kievan Rus'.  She was alone.  Apart from
Kyiv, no other Rus'
existed.
It is true that you
cannot name any
other Rus' except Kievan Rus', because it was
only Kievan Rus'.   Yes.
Here's the thing.
And about the fact that at some point I just
stop-stop I go to Wikipedia,
yes, Rus', Ancient Rus', yes.  So, uh,
it existed from 882 to 1240,
yes, when the Mongols captured Kyiv,
the capital was Kyiv from 882, yes, until 1240.
That is, Rus' existed from 882. Yes.   Yes.
And there wasn't one before?
Before this there was no Rus'.   Yes.   Yes.
He
also came in the story, also in the Tale of Bygone
Years it is written like this.  Oleg came and created
Rus'.
The capital of Rus' is Ladoga.
No.
Stop, stop, stop.  Show me, show me where.  In
the Tale of Time.  Where in what summer?
Veliky Novgorod.
Again.  Again.  In those years, Rus' did
not yet exist.  So, Rus' did not exist.  Vladimir,
when did Rus appear?
Then Moscow, then St. Petersburg,
then
when did Russia appear, in what year did
Rus' appear?
800 62.
Where in Ladoga did Ryuri Krus create?
Now.  Stop.  Oh, oh, I'll put on different glasses,
so they look better.
Ladoga is, in short, one of the villages
in the Fatel list of the Tale of Bygone
Years; Ladoga is named as the first residence of
Prince Rurik.  However, not all historians
support this version.  Once again,
everything.
Veliky Novgorod, sixty-
fourty-two.  Listen,
go ahead and open some official one.  What is
your name?  Here I am,
according to some summers,
what is your name
in the city where his residence was located
in Rurik's city.  The city was built
from the eighty-second to the year 1243.
It was Kyiv.  Anyway, listen, let's do it this way.   Let's do it this way
.  Look.  OK.  When, uh,
Okay, let's do it this way.  When this Rurik
sailed in Ladoga, what country
was Kyiv in?
Oh, I don't know these things.  Here, here I have
written down several cities that
served as capitals.
Where do you read this?
Well,
where do you read?  Well, what kind of source is this?
Alice's quick response.
What's the quick answer?  I don't need Alice.
Give me an official source.  Well, how
can it be official?  I'm telling you,
Ladoga.  Ours call it the first
capital, and all historians support this
version.
Once again there was no capital of Ladoga.
In general, Rus' was not Rus' then.   Well, here it is
written in the Ipatiev copy of
the Tale of Bygone Years.  Ladogan.
Listen, come on, listen, come on.  Okay, let me
not push you around Rurik.
Fine.  What you?  Here, here it is written,
everything is written.  You have written Alice
wrote.  Yes,
open it.  Have you even read the
chronicle?  Yes, I read the letter of the named years,
right?  You, you read.  Do you know how it
begins?
I didn't read it at all.
Here, open it and read the first lines of the
Tale of Bygone Years, that after the flood
the sons of Noah went there, Ipheth there, Ham
there.  In short, a biblical story.
Actually,
the Tale of Bygone Years is a
work of fiction.  Okay, so what if
Kyiv was the first capital, so what?
And the
only thing, right?  No, nothing, you just
start telling stories there.  What follows from this
now?
Nothing follows.  It's just that, well, Kyiv was the
only capital of Rus'.  Well, what's the
problem?  Well, that's all.
Moscow, too, was never the capital of
Rus'.
Yeah.  And the fact is that this period of
time, when Kyiv was the capital,
was called Kievan Rus.  Ah, and
Muscovite Rus was called And which
section is called Muscovite Rus?
Why no friends?
Well, because
when Kyiv was the capital, it was a very
long period of time, right?  And the other
sections weren't named, right?  Why not
call it Muscovite Rus,
St. Petersburg Rus?   Well
, that's why.   Yes.
Fine.  Can you ask Alice
when Moscow was the capital of Rus'?  Well,
ask Alice when Moscow was the
capital of Rus'?  Never.
Your
cat is already howling there, it wants you.
Cat.  The cat is 21 years old, he doesn’t
understand anything
[laughter]
go ahead and ask Alice when Moscow was
Ask Alice when Moscow was the
capital of Rus'.  Let's.
She she is with me she is with me she is deaf,
blind, old.
Well, in short,
21 years, 150 years in human terms.  An apple is
not far from the apples for Katya.   An
apple falls within an apple's category.
From the apple tree.  Let's.  Ask
Lista again when Moscow was the capital of
Rus'.  And why does he ask?
What?  What?  What are you following? Because you
read that Moscow was not the capital of
Rus'.
Yes, it's written here.  Alice, tell me, when
was Moscow the capital of Rus'?
Oh, wait, I'm going in the wrong direction.  I didn't click
anywhere.
Will you turn on the [laughter] sound?  Yes, go ahead and
ask.
Ah,
go ahead and ask.  So that I can hear
Alice's answer.
Oh my god, I'm already tired.  I don't know.   Go ahead and
ask.  When was Moscow the capital of
Rus'?  You said that Moscow was there.
Where should I press?
I don't know where you need to click on Alice
.  Pet Alice.  I don't know.
This is your Alice.
Alice?  Alice,
when was Moscow the capital of Rus'?
Okay, stop.
Alice, when was Moscow the capital of Rus'?
Moscow became the center of the unification of Russian
lands and, in fact, the capital of Rus' in the 10th
century.  The key stage of stopping is
seen
in the 10th century.  And ask Alice, like, are
these really Russians?
Oh, no need, I won't ask anything.
Wait, wait.
Ask, until what year did
Rus' exist?  Ask Alice until what year
Rus' existed.  In the 10th century there was no longer any
Rus'.   Oh
well.
The Mongols captured it in the 10th century.  Ask.
You defeated me.  That's it, I'm tired of you
already.
Come on and go to the cat, I'll satisfy you.  You
never told me.  Who are you?  How do you call
this one?
Yes, yes, I remember.  I am still my
Father's sweetheart.
[laughter] Let's
go.
Kashaka,
how are they with this Rus'?  Rus'.  Maryurik, they are the
first capital, right?  This is a section of Kievan Rus
.  But why weren’t there Moscow
Russes, Leningrad Russes?  Yes.  Like,
subscribe, comment.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.  Here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
in the Telegram channel is posted for those who don’t have
Telegram or who don’t use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.